[
  {
      "question": "Which Activation Function in Machine Learning has a range between 0 and positive infinity?",
      "options": ["ReLu", "Sigmoid", "Tanh"],
      "correct_answer": "ReLu"
  },
  {
      "question": "What is tensor in tensor algebra?",
      "options": ["An algebraic object that describes a multilinear relationship between sets of algebraic objects related to a vector space", "An algebraic object that describes a unilinear relationship between sets of algebraic objects related to a vector space"],
      "correct_answer": "An algebraic object that describes a multilinear relationship between sets of algebraic objects related to a vector space"
  },
  {
    "question": "Technically Tensors are multi-dimensional arrays with a uniform type (dtype):",
    "options": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct_answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "When it comes to training time in TensorFlow and PyTorch libraries:",
    "options": ["TensorFlow has higher training time", "PyTorch has higher training time", "Times are the same"],
    "correct_answer": "TensorFlow has higher training time"
  },
  {
    "question": "When it comes to flexibility of TensorFlow and PyTorch libraries:",
    "options": ["TensorFlow is more flexible", "PyTorch is more flexible"],
    "correct_answer": "PyTorch is more flexible"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the most promising and widely adopted languages for data science, machine learning, and statistical computing:",
    "options": ["Python", "C++", "Basic", "PHP"],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "question": "... is the most widely used language in the Jupyter ecosystem:",
    "options": ["R", "Julia", "Python"],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "question": "PyTorch is an open source machine learning and deep learning framework:",
    "options": ["True", "False", "I have never heard of it, so the package does not exits"],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Scalar, Vector, Matrix are different types of tensor",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "In pytorch scalar tensor is created like i.e.:",
    "options": ["scalar = torch.tensor(7,7)", "scalar = torch.tensor(7)", "scalar = torch.tensor()"],
    "correct_answer": "scalar = torch.tensor(7)"
  },
  {
    "question": "A scalar refers to a:",
    "options": ["single numeric value", "can be a string"],
    "correct_answer": "single numeric value"
  },
  {
    "question": "Put in logical order:",
    "options": ["scalar/matrix/vector", "matrix/scalar/vector", "scalar/vector/matrix"],
    "correct_answer": "scalar/vector/matrix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tensors, in general, are the fundamental building blocks in PyTorch:",
    "options": ["definitely yes", "of course not"],
    "correct_answer": "definitely yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tensors can work with integers only:",
    "options": ["No, tensors in PyTorch can work with various numeric data types", "Yes, they work only with integers"],
    "correct_answer": "No, tensors in PyTorch can work with various numeric data types"
  },
  {
    "question": "Random Tensors are important, because:",
    "options": ["because they are not important", "the way many nn learn is they start with tensors full of random numbers and adjust random numbers to better represent data and so on"],
    "correct_answer": "the way many nn learn is they start w tensors full of random numbers and adjust random numbers to better represent data and so on"
  }

]
 